I hope you got your coffee or your drink or your beer ready because today is going to be an interesting video.
A lot of see-through spandex items from LeoHacks.
I have quite a few LeoHacks videos on my channel already.
And this one I didn't try anything on yet so I am curious as well.
Let's find out how everything looks and how see-through everything really is.
see-through I hate this word of course we're still on YouTube so I am wearing a lingerie set beneath
everything because it's see-through and I don't want to get this video taken down or rated 18 plus
or whatever so yeah I think you get the idea of how the items look anyway and this is kind of a
cool design option I don't know I like the combination with lingerie you can actually see
that being said that is really interesting or unusual color for me because normally I don't
wear white at all so I like the black part of the lingerie it doesn't make this too white in general
and it's really really smooth and soft you can also see the shine of the lights
going to turn around really quick because there's not much going on at the back I love that there
is a clasp in my neck to pull the sides together otherwise we have the kind of racing back and I
think it is a really cute design and a really cute piece of lingerie itself the bodysuit I don't know
would not wear this in the public pool so I don't think it's a swimsuit at
least not for me okay since this is really really wide I'm going to take
something that's darker let's see what's inside a catsuit so I'll quickly change
Now that is something right up my alley because it's black!
So I love black catsuits and this is a really cool look with the underwear peeking through.
I mean, I would definitely wear this to party.
It also is so smooth, it's basically slippery.
I was sitting on a chair putting on shoes and I kind of slid off the chair.
Just a second, I'll show you.
I'm like sliding on so when I cross my legs over they slip on each other.
That's how smooth it is.
Which is kind of funny.
And it still looks good.
I know a lot of people say in the comments that they don't like the logo here but I think
that's just part of the design and that's part of the items you decide on.
So I have no problem with it.
I think it's kind of cool.
I'm switching between colors.
So next up is something gray or silver.
And it's just a leggings.
So I'll have to see if I need to wear top or just my bra.
I love the wide waistband here.
And I think it fits really good.
I'm wearing size large for everything today.
And the color is a bit light for me.
I also have a bodysuit that is kind of a darker shade of grey.
So I'm going to put the bodysuit on top of that and see how it looks together.
It's not ideal with the panty lines and the lines of the waistband here together with the bodysuit but I think you get the idea.
And you can check out the LeoHex store because they have basically everything in multiple colors and multiple options.
I think there are also stay ups in this material.
And I just realized that the leggings have like a small logo here which is only the L of LeoHex which is kind of cool.
and not the full signature here so something different
I love the darker color and I also was just sitting here like this and I said wow the
leggings is super comfortable so it does not um it does not how do you say it in English
It doesn't pinch. It doesn't pinch. It doesn't pinch somewhere. It is not too tight. The material is super stretchy and really comfortable.
I'm also not sure about the color. I chose green for this outfit but I'm not sure it fits. Maybe I should go to orange or red.
So maybe I should just switch outfit again and find a matching color.
one last color it is something like gold nude bronze mashup between everything
and it works okay together with my skin color I guess
and it also shines a lot in the light I love that about everything
just checking myself in the mirror sorry
okay so I think we had black light gray dark gray um white and this one and a lot of multiple
body suits catsuit leggings so check out leo hacks and click on the link in the description text
also if you want to see more and behind the scenes check out my patreon
when you order there check the sizing table as I said I'm wearing large and everything I also wear
x4 large it depends x4 large is a bit more comfortable although everything was really
comfortable today so I'm good and I hope you enjoyed the video see you around in the next one bye